<omni_shot_configuration>
    <!-- RENDERING TELEMETRY SPECIFICATIONS -->
    <camera_profile>
        Extreme macro lens configuration. Fixed tilt-shift lens axis establishing a hyper-shallow depth of field. Razor-sharp focal tracking locked strictly onto the crystalline structural plane of the iris and individual eyelash roots. Background drop-off collapses into a heavy, smooth bokeh. Camera executes a continuous, tense micro-zoom directly into the absolute geometric center of the pupil, transforming into an exponential forward push.
    </camera_profile>
    
    <!-- THE FOUNDATIONAL LAB COLOR MATRIX (DYNAMIC METADATA FLIP) -->
    <color_grading_matrix ratio="Standard_to_Inverted_Dynamic_Flip">
        <phase_1_macro_focus duration="0.0s-3.5s" weighting="Standard_60_30_10">
            60% Base Architecture: Rich lavender iris filaments and deep slate-teal (#124559) perimeter shadow shading. 30% Dynamic Energy: Crisp, miniaturized electric-cyan (#00E5FF) and jade-teal (#00C49A) control panel graphics perfectly mirror-reflected inside the dark pupil void. 10% Disruptive Focal Pop: Hot coral pink-red (#FF6B6B) active alert telemetry indicators pulsing within the mirrored grid.
        </phase_1_macro_focus>
        <phase_2_lens_overexposure duration="3.5s-6.0s" weighting="Inverted_60_30_10_White_Hot_Glare">
            60% Color Splash: Blinding, pure white-hot glare flood washing out all spatial structures. 30% Dynamic Materials: Over-saturated, expanding electric-cyan neon halos and bleeding coral-red light paths. 10% Base Architecture: Fractured, disintegrating slate-teal silhouettes of the iris perimeter as the lens completely clips.
        </phase_2_lens_overexposure>
    </color_grading_matrix>
    
    <!-- LIGHTING & REFRACTIVE PHYSICS -->
    <lighting_and_materials>
        Analytical visual simulator pass. Volumetric light emissions casting directly from the miniaturized console readouts. Sharp glass caustics and complex fluid light refractions playing across the wet, translucent curvature of the cornea. Pronounced rainbow spectral edge separation (chromatic aberration) localized at the absolute perimeter boundaries of the expanding pupil reflection as the camera passes through the focal plane.
    </lighting_and_materials>

    <!-- VISUAL COMPOSITION & TIMELINE ACTION -->
    <scene_action>
        An extreme close-up macro shot focusing entirely on a single striking lavender eye. The smooth skin textures and sharp eyelashes are rendered with microscopic clarity. Reflected inside the glossy black pupil, a complex grid of spaceship control telemetry displays pulses with rising energy. From 0.0s to 3.5s, the camera executes a smooth micro-zoom directly into the center of the pupil. At 3.5s, the zoom accelerates exponentially; the glowing cyan and coral neon reflections expand outward, completely overwhelming the lens boundaries. By 6.0s, the frame has dissolved entirely into a seamless, pure white-hot glare. Absolute structural stability; zero eye color shifting, zero multi-pupil deformities.
    </scene_action>

    <!-- DECOUPLED SPATIAL AUDIO STREAMS -->
    <audio_system_streams>
        <music_track semantic="Visual_Mood">
            A low-frequency analog sub-bass drone creates an intense foundation. At 3.5s, a high-pass filter opens rapidly, transforming the drone into an ascending electronic riser that thins into a crystalline, whistling high-frequency pitch at the moment of total overexposure.
        </music_track>
        <effects_track semantic="Event_Timing">
            0.0s - 3.5s: A cyclic, low-amplitude cascade of digitized data packet chime sweeps operating at -18dB, speeding up in a strict delay-loop pattern. Exactly at 3.5s, a massive, pressurized pneumatic rush layers onto the mix, building into a clean white-noise wash that peaks at 6.0s to match the white glare.
        </effects_track>
        <speech_track semantic="Dialogue_Prosody">
            <speaker ID="Vespera" status="Silent" />
        </speech_track>
    </audio_system_streams>

    <!-- OBJECT-BASED SPATIAL METADATA -->
    <spatial_metadata_anchors>
        <pupil_telemetry_source coordinates="Cartesian(0.0, 1.2, 0.0)" tracking="Z-Axis_Camera_Push">
            Digital data chime sweeps originate from dead-center space, expanding their stereo width parameters symmetrically across the X and Y axes as the camera enters the pupil volume.
        </pupil_telemetry_source>
    </spatial_metadata_anchors>
</omni_shot_configuration>