<omni_shot_configuration>
    <!-- RENDERING TELEMETRY & LARGE-FORMAT IMPACT CONSTRAINTS -->
    <camera_profile>
        Massive wide-angle sci-fi cinematic shot. Axis layout simulates a large-format 15-perf 70mm cinematography framework, intentionally subverting standard macro diorama limits into extreme focal geometry scale. Camera executes a violent, high-velocity kinetic pull-back snap-zoom pass starting precisely at 1.0s. Zero smooth curves; camera trajectory matches a severe backward coordinate displacement vector, tracking the speed of the accelerating vessel.
    </camera_profile>
    
    <!-- THE FOUNDATIONAL LAB COLOR MATRIX (INVERTED HIGH-ENERGY EXPLOSION) -->
    <color_grading_matrix ratio="Inverted_60_30_10_High_Energy_Splash">
        <color_splash weight="60%"> A blinding, volatile, overexposed flood of pure electric-cyan (#00E5FF) and coral-red (#FF6B6B) plasma glare exploding outward from a central engine core array, completely clipping highlight fields across the frame center.</color_splash>
        <dynamic_materials weight="30%"> Shifting neon-indigo energy arcs and burning turquoise lightning rifts fracturing across the surrounding space-time fabric.</dynamic_materials>
        <base_architecture weight="10%"> Towering launch bay geometric columns, the terminal dock framework, and the main spaceship hull are reduced entirely to sharp, hard-edged solid-black silhouette matrices completely detached from background texture.</base_architecture>
    </color_grading_matrix>
    
    <!-- OPTICAL & WARP PHYSICS -->
    <lighting_and_materials>
        Volumetric light ray beams cutting through dense air grids under massive kinetic stress. Intense refractive caustics creating a lens overexposure bloom effect. Violent rainbow spectral edge separation (chromatic aberration) tearing across the high-contrast perimeter boundaries of the solid-black silhouettes. Shifting environmental lighting layers update instantly across structural edges.
    </lighting_and_materials>

    <!-- VISUAL COMPOSITION & TIMELINE ACTION -->
    <scene_action>
        [0.0s - 1.0s]: Static wide shot. The solid-black silhouette of the spaceship sits locked within the vertical launch bay columns; the background console fields pulse with high-contrast electric-cyan indicators.
        [1.0s - 4.0s]: Massive ignition event. Sixty percent of the frame turns into a volatile flood of bright electric-cyan and coral-red plasma overexposure glare. The silhouetted ship accelerates instantly from a standstill out of top-center, leaving a brilliant, burning solid-black streak across a fracturing space-time rift. Camera executes a rapid, violent kinetic pull-back snap-zoom tracking the launch. Zero facial features, zero legible text, zero smooth gradients.
    </scene_action>

    <!-- DECOUPLED SPATIAL AUDIO STREAMS -->
    <audio_system_streams>
        <music_track semantic="Visual_Mood">
            0.0s - 1.0s: Silent mid-register step-sequencer layer held behind a high-pass filter. Exactly at 1.0s: The music bed drops out completely, leaving only a sustained high-pass delay echo tail that clip-fades into an extreme low-frequency sub-bass analog riser.
        </music_track>
        <effects_track semantic="Event_Timing">
            Timestamp 1.0s: A massive, structural low-frequency engine compression thrum rolling flatly at -6dB, transitioning instantly into a high-transient electrical whip-snap sound event and a tearing open-air white-noise vacuum hiss that holds a long decay scale until 4.0s.
        </effects_track>
        <speech_track semantic="Dialogue_Prosody">
            <speaker ID="Systems_AI" status="Silent" />
        </speech_track>
    </audio_system_streams>

    <!-- OBJECT-BASED SPATIAL METADATA -->
    <spatial_metadata_anchors>
        <plasma_core_explosion coordinates="Cartesian(0.0, 25.0, 2.0)" tracking="Dynamic_Warp_Trajectory">
            Low-frequency propulsion thrum and energy tearing sound components are encoded as a discrete spatial audio object, moving instantly down a negative Z-axis vector from 25.0 meters to 2.0 meters to perfectly mirror the physics of the structural breakout sequence.
        </plasma_core_explosion>
    </spatial_metadata_anchors>
</omni_shot_configuration>